Press play. Subtitles appear.
200+ languages. One app:  tryray.app
Do you think you're ready
for a second chance at love?
Cupid does. His arrow awaits
at CupidsPlan.com.
where right now.
thousands of people
are searching for
someone just like you.
KYW news time 8:12 a.m..
72 and sunny in
Independence Hall.
Time now for
traffic on the twos.
We got a stalled car on the blue
route just before Springfield.
Full count. man on second
here in the third inning.
Cottman delivers.
Turner smashes it
back up the middle.
He'll score easily
and extend their lead.
-Uh. morning.
-Morning.
Did you eat. Em?
I made some scrambled
eggs and scrapple.
-I'm gonna be late.
-Okay.
Well. anything you want
for dinner tonight?
I. uh. could stop by
the Acme on my way...
I have... I have work.
Right. Big night.
Maybe I'll drop by
for a water ice.
There's a package there for you.
Alright.
Have a good day.
Look at that.
You can own your own island.
Who picks up your trash?
Your trash?
-Yeah.
-That's where your head goes?
I mean. seriously. if
you're on an island.
are there like trash boats?
-Trash boats?
-Yeah.
If you're on an island. you're
not thinking about trash.
Thinking...
you know. "Where's my hammock?"
You ever experiment with
that online dating stuff?
A couple times.
What happened?
People.
They can just
Google you nowadays.
Dig up your whole life.
See all your fuck-ups.
So. you use a fake name.
Instead of Cliff
Broward. be like...
Diff Moward.
-Diff Moward?
-Yeah.
The fuck kinda name
is Diff Moward?
That's awful.
I don't wanna use a
fake name. you know?
Yeah.
I'm not fucking
hiding who I am.
Yeah.
I think... I think
maybe I'm ready.
Ready for what?
-What are you ready for?
-Mm-mm.
Like. to share my life
with someone again.
I don't know.
I don't mind being alone.
Yeah. no shit. You're a monk.
You always have been.
Not a monk. Monks pray.
We're built
different. you and me.
I need a...
I need a life companion.
You know. July will be a year.
Since Karen left.
The longer she's gone. the
less I think she's comin' back.
Well...
try the online stuff then.
Who knows?
Maybe you'll find
your life companion.
Beauty to your beast.
Fuck off.
Fucking Diff Moward. fucking...
Oh.
Uh. sorry about that. uh...
Tom Brandis.
Kyle.
Here you go. Uh.
take one of these.
-Recent grad?
-Yeah. Widener.
Congratulations.
What's your degree in?
Accounting. which doesn't
exactly make much sense for me
to be stopping at an FBI booth.
You'd be surprised.
I majored in philosophy
as an undergrad.
Then I became a priest
for eight years.
And I'm here now talking to you
about what the FBI has to offer.
We have a very wide reach
here at the bureau. and...
This is like an
actual job in the FBI?
Well. I'm a field agent.
Normally that's my...
just taking a little time off.
I'll be back on
assignment again soon.
hunting down the bad guys.
Watch out. bad guys.
Check out the STEM program.
Given your math background.
that might be a very good fit.
Great. I'll look it over.
Wait. Here's more.
Boys have been very busy.
Ooh.
Go in tonight. before
the money moves.
♪ Look at the ivy on
that old clinging wall ♪
What is this kid
wearing? Jesus.
Oh. my God! What the fuck?
Yo. Yo. yo. Peach-boy!
What's up. what's up. what's up?
What's good?
What up?
I'm spoken for.
That's what's good.
Fuck's that mean?
Gave my angel the ring.
Did the rose petals and all.
Your angel?
This that brunette you were
talking to a few weeks ago?
We're just two bodies. one soul.
Aw. man.
It's a spiritual
thing. you know?
Yeah. we're happy
for you. Peach-boy.
Listen. do you remember
that house on Murdoch?
Place we've been staking
out the past couple weeks?
We're going in tonight.
This will make for a
very nice down payment
on the wedding venue.
We saw your ass when
we were pulling up.
-What are you staring at my ass for?
-Pick your fuckin' pants up.
-No.
-Huh?
Midnight. Peaches.
See yous tonight.
We had a very good meeting
with the judge this morning.
Oh.
-Great.
-Yeah.
He confirmed sentencing
for June 12th at 9 a.m.
How long is he
gonna go away for?
Third degree. we're looking at
anywhere from 5 to 15 years.
But that length of time
will depend on the
family impact statement.
Have you. uh. given
any further thought?
Matt. I decided I wasn't
gonna make the statement.
Right. You're not
gonna make a statement?
No.
But when we sat down last time.
Emily expressed interest in
talking on her brother's behalf.
Yeah. I... I
haven't had a chance
to ask her about it recently.
Wow. Not... not to
pressure anyone.
It's just. since the crime
occurred within the family unit.
Judge Adams will place a lot
of weight on this statement
when determining
Ethan's sentence.
I'll talk to her
about it tonight.
Ah! Holy shit!
I scared you. Uncle Trash!
You did. you definitely did.
Uncle Trash. guess what?
Oh. no.
-I'm not falling for that game.
-Chicken butt!
No more chicken
butt jokes. Wyatt.
Hey. sweetheart. Good day?
-Pretty good.
-Mwah.
Oh.
You didn't tell me Cliff
was coming for dinner.
That's alright. you don't
gotta cook for me. Maeve.
-Comin' in hot.
-I'll. uh...
throw in some Bagel
Bites or something.
Yeah.
It stinks in here!
Did you fart?
-Are you serious right now?
-What?
I just made all this food and
you're eating M&M ice cream.
Don't even think about
using the yellow towel!
-Harp. will you pull up a chair?
-Yeah.
-What'd you make? Let's take a look.
-Got it.
Oh. that looks good.
What... I see some corn.
Uh. spinach? Or is that
marshmallow on top?
-Is anybody listening?
-Cheese.
Oh. That looks fantastic.
It's a Ree Drummond recipe.
-Make yourself useful and call Wyatt in.
-It's hot!
Dinner. bud.
We're having. uh.
Bree Drummer's recipe.
and it looks
absolutely delicious.
Alright!
That looks like dog food.
-Wyatt!
-Hey. hey.
I... I like marshmallows.
Dad. guess what?
-Chicken butt.
-Nope.
Chicken butthole.
Oh. man.
Can I have something better?
What?
Hey. Hey. You gotta be nice.
You gotta be nice.
Have a good night. Enjoy.
Hello. miss.
Can I get a black cherry
water ice. please?
What size would you like?
Extra large. Is there any other?
How's she doing in there. guy?
Employee of the Month material?
You know. I... I don't know
if we do that here. but...
Don't worry about it. I'm
just... I'm just kidding around.
Wow. How much is that?
-Dad. it's fine.
-No. no.
I pay like everyone else.
Love how they have the
cherry bits in there.
-There's people behind you. Dad.
-Mm.
Can I talk to you for a
minute. when you get a chance?
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Busy night. huh?
Yeah. crazy.
Little Matty Pearson over
there. he... he grew up. huh?
What do you wanna
talk about. Dad?
I just...
I sat down with our lawyer
Matt Kerrigan earlier.
and he asked if you had decided
to. uh. make a sentencing
statement for your brother.
Do I need to tell
him. like. right now?
Like now? Like
tonight. or can I...
No. I mean. yeah. no.
-Um...
-You don't. no.
Okay.
We got time. it's
just. they're...
y-you definitely
have time here.
Yeah. I should... I should
probably get back to work.
No. Of course.
Opening night. huh?
Yep.
And then. Uncle Billy and I
saw the great dragon.
And we jumped onto
its wings and...
We flew way up into the sky...
where a new kingdom existed.
The dragon kill Uncle Billy?
Is that why he's dead?
No. the dragon didn't do that.
Come here. give me your hand.
'Cause Uncle Billy...
is right there.
-Can you feel him?
-Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
'Cause I feel him. too.
Every second of every moment
of every day. right here.
He's in your heart. too.
What do you think about that?
Cool.
It is cool.
You're cool.
Save a little for me. huh?
Geez. Robbie.
Ooh!
Maybe knock next time?
Copy that.
Also. you're allowed to do
what you want to do. Maeve.
I'm your uncle. not.
you know. like...
house police.
You're 20 now.
I'm 21.
Twenty-one? When
did that happen?
Nine months ago.
Well. shit.
We gotta celebrate.
Get a night out on the books.
What do you want?
Cliff and I are headed out.
Yous don't spend enough
time together already?
An old friend's in town.
Taking him up to Hopper's.
Don't come back with a DUI.
Nah. They can't catch me.
I know these roads like
the back of my hand.
What's so funny?
It's the third time you checked.
You think the
bullets crawled out?
Fuck you laughing at back there?
Crawling bullets.
What the hell are we
listening to. anyway?
Transportative. isn't it?
Trans-what-ative?
Takes you away
from your reality.
puts you in another.
Close your eyes and get
transported. Peach-boy.
Now. imagine you're
on a white sand beach
surrounded by blue. blue ocean.
And there are women.
Beautiful women.
-And they're dancing.
-Uh-huh.
They're dancing.
Everyone's fucking happy as
shit to be on that beach.
And you don't got a
care in the world.
One of those beautiful women.
she comes walking over to you.
and she says...
-"Dance with me. Peach-boy."
-Mm!
Ooh! Ooh!
Oh. boy. I don't think angel's
gonna be too happy about that.
Jesus.
Fuck. man.
The hell is that. anyway?
Every time. you
do the same thing.
When I was a little kid.
my brother and I went
swimming in the quarry.
January. February.
it didn't matter.
You jump into water that cold.
your heart can explode
from the shock.
So. you take some water.
you put it on both
your shoulders.
Your body gets used
to the temperature.
and your heart slows
so it doesn't explode.
We're not jumping
into freezing water.
We're robbing a
fucking trap house.
It's calming. Peach-boy.
-Where's the money?
-Fuck you!
We've been watching
you. motherfucker.
You've been selling
off for three days now.
Where's the fucking money?
Where's the fucking money?!
Over there. Toilet.
We're out.
Shit.
Yeah. I have called that
asshole 15 times. at least.
and it always goes to voicemail.
What's... what's goin'
on? Is he avoiding me?
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
No. what... what do
you mean. concessions?
Your side fucked itself
in the ass with no lube.
Own that and fix it.
Yeah. Thank you.
You too.
Jesus fucking hell.
"No lube." Haven't
heard that before.
-Old dogs need new tricks.
-Mm.
Yeah.
I brought you some. uh. fresh
tomatoes from the garden.
Wonderful. Thank you.
You wanted to see me?
Fucking SAC. denied
my extension.
September 1st. I'm
being forcibly retired.
Why didn't you say something?
Jesus Christ. Kath.
why didn't you tell me?
Because I didn't
know till last night.
-Why? I mean...
-I don't know.
They want youth. and I'm
an unrefined old bitch.
-I'm sorry. Kath.
-Yeah.
What are you gonna do?
My mother wants me to
take her to Ireland
one last time.
She's 93 fuckin' years
old. Can you imagine?
-Sorry. Kath.
-No. Anywho.
That's not why I called you in.
I need you back
out in the field.
-Now?
-Unfortunately. yes.
-Kath. I mean. come on. I-It's not a great time.
-No. I know.
-The timing is shit. I know.
-You know what's going on with me.
-Yeah. "shit's" a good word for it. Kath.
-I don't have any choice. Tom.
The SAC called me.
They want me to put
together a task force.
-I know. I'm sorry.
-Shit.
I assigned Maria
Herrera to lead.
but she got ordered to bed rest.
-What is it?
-I don't know. it's something
about a... a leaky uterus.
-What's the job?
-Sorry.
There's been a spate
of home invasions
in Montco and Delco Counties.
Two-. sometimes three-man
crew. Middle of the night.
They're targeting drug houses.
-Hm.
-Through DEA informants.
we know of at least nine
houses that have been hit.
And of those nine. seven belong
to members of a motorcycle gang.
-uh. the Dark Hearts.
-Mm.
You ever run across them?
I brushed with them
in Violent Crimes.
They just found two
bodies last week
behind a concrete
plant in Ridley.
They're low-level
distributors.
but the Dark Hearts
are retaliating.
-Blaming other gangs?
-They're spinnin'.
We need to find this crew
before a turf war escalates.
-How long you need me?
-Budgeted for four weeks.
but Maria hired a team.
State Trooper Elizabeth Stover
outta Lancaster Barracks.
Uh...
Sergeant Detective Aleah
Clinton. Chester Department.
and CD Anthony Grasso.
He works Organized
Crime for the county.
It's not exactly a wealth
of experience. Kath.
No. it's Task. Tom.
You know. we're not talking
the tip of the spear here.
You gotta work with
what you're given.
-Where's headquarters?
-You're in luck.
Vice just confiscated a
lovely little stash house
out near Kennett Square.
Congratulations.
It's now your Tri-County
Task Headquarters.
Yeah. budget cuts
at their finest.
What can I say? You know. it's
all that money we're wasting
on those fancy brochures you
can't get anyone to take.
Yeah.
How's the family. Tom?
Emily okay?
Yeah.
Thanks for the tomatoes.
Don't break! Don't break!
Oh. shit!
-Whoo!
Whoo!
The hell?
-New lead.
-Already?
Let's go scope it out.
That one there.
Careful.
Afternoon.
What's the matter?
Motherfucker was
looking at me funny.
-He's not lookin' at you.
-Damn right he was.
Looking through you.
like everyone else.
This is the one we've
been asking for.
Unless you're having
second thoughts.
A beautiful weekend ahead.
For those looking to
escape to the shore.
this might be the best
weekend of the year to do it.
Bright and sunny with temps at
the boardwalk expected to reach...
Next.
Hi. I'm here dropping a
suit off for an inmate.
What's the inmate's name?
Ethan Brandis.
And what's your
relationship to the inmate?
I'm his father. It's for
his sentencing hearing.
And will you be visiting
your son today as well?
-I'm sorry?
-Next visitation session
starts in about 30
minutes. so if you want me
-to put you on the list. I can do that right now.
-Uh. no.
I don't... I don't want to.
I'm... I'm just dropping off.
Yeah!
What do you think?
These ones or these ones?
Uh... big hoops.
Great minds.
-What's he like?
-My date?
Mm. Six out of ten.
Could use a shave.
The ass is kinda flat.
Then why go out with him?
Well. it's not so
much about him.
It's just wantin'
to be out. You know?
Listen to music. Dancin'.
Talkin' about anything other
than chicken butt holes
and farts.
Good to have you here with
us in parts unknown. USA.
As always. we're surrounded
by boxes of records.
CDs. 45s. we have
eight-track tapes.
We got all kinds of
stuff laying around here.
Kick back. settle in.
relax. get comfortable.
This is "The Many
Moods of Ben Vaughn."
Glad to have you here with us.
We're starting off
this evening with Caamp
to give you a mellow
start to your evening.
Lots of good times
and good tunes ahead.
♪ Honey. honey. get the
kids in the car now ♪
♪ Put the cash in the trunk.
get the keys. let's go ♪
♪ Keep your lights down ♪
♪ And I'll meet you in Idaho ♪
♪ I know you'll miss
me. I'm barely 50 ♪
♪ Ain't coming with me
are all the debts I owe ♪
♪ Don't have to kiss me. just
bear with me ♪ -♪ With me ♪
♪ And I'll be back
someday. I hope ♪
♪ And I know you'll
miss me. I'm barely 50 ♪
♪ Ain't coming with me
are all the debts I owe ♪
♪ Don't have to kiss
me. just bear with me ♪
♪ And I'll be back
someday. I hope ♪
♪ I hope ♪
And this is the grand hall.
That you as a baby?
I was way cuter then.
Oh. shh...
That's my cousin's room.
And this... is my room.
My palace.
Wow.
It's... wow.
It's very. uh. artsy.
You're like an artist or...
I'm nothin'. Absolutely nothin'.
Blank slate. I like it.
You wanna watch a movie?
Not really.
I'd rather do somethin' else.
We just have to
be really quiet.
-Oh.
-Can you be really quiet?
I'm sorry.
Sorry. sorry. I'm sorry.
-I was smoking. I'm sorry.
-Bro. back off her.
-What the hell. Uncle Robbie?
-I was smoking. it's my bad.
-Hey. easy.
-Back off.
or I'll drop your fucking ass!
-Come here.
-Robbie. come on!
Fuck you. punk-ass bitch!
Robbie. come on!
Robbie! Wait. Tripp!
Get the fuck outta here!
-Fuck you people.
-Wait. Tripp. I'm sorry.
Are you just gonna. like.
linger behind me. or...
Sorry.
I. uh...
just wanted to apologize.
It's fine. I don't care.
It's just. you know. raised his
hands at me in my house and...
Your house?
Uh... okay.
Uh. my brother's house.
No. My house.
Passed down to me
when my dad died.
which I allowed you to move
into when you lost yours.
So. you know what?
I should be allowed to get
drunk and make out with someone
without being worried you're gonna
jump out of the fuckin' closet.
Okay. let's... let's. uh.
talk about this tomorrow.
No. we're not talkin'
about it tomorrow.
What's the definition
of insanity?
-Staying in one place. or...
-I don't think that's the saying.
I think it's about.
like. trial and error.
Well. that's my sayin'.
Maeve's definition of insanity
is stayin' at the freak farm
thinking anything's
gonna change.
There. Just coined it.
Wow.
Uh. I...
I guess I didn't realize
you were so unhappy.
Well. I am.
-I'm miserable.
-Okay. okay.
Okay. well. then it's good
we're having this conversation.
Maeve. what do...
what do you want?
What... what is it that
you're missin' here?
I don't know what I'm missin'
'cause I never had anything.
-I thought we were in this together as a team.
-You know. first. my dad dies.
then Karen takes off.
And I'm here raising
her kids. Your kids.
I mean. what the fuck do
I know about raising kids?
I need to make a
life for myself.
-You... you want money? Is that it?
-No. it's not about money.
It's about not having the weight of
the goddamn world on my shoulders.
We can talk about me buying
you out of the house.
Buy me out?
With what?
Oh. the money from whatever
crazy-ass shit you and Cliff
are doing out there in
the middle of the night?
Maeve.
-I don't wanna fuckin' hear it. Robbie.
Don't wanna hear.
Don't wanna know.
It's not like that.
It is different.
-I don't wanna fuckin' hear it. It's like my dad!
-I'm doing it for this family
-so we can stay in this house.
-You're my fucking dad.
-Lie after lie...
-Okay. you know what?
-...after fucking lie!
-You wanna go so bad. go ahead.
We'll be fine without you.
We'll certainly
fuckin' eat better.
Fuck you for sayin' that.
Pack up your shit and get out.
-It's not your house. asshole!
-It's not yours either!
It's my brother's. My brother's.
I can handle things
here on my own.
If I actually believed that
for even half a second...
I'd have left a long time ago.
Maeve. please don't leave.
Come here.
Eddie. I can literally.
like. see myself
in the furniture
gallery right now.
and I'm talking to this
fucking salesperson saying.
"Hey. yeah. that recliner. that's
the fucking recliner I want."
That's not the fucking point.
What do you mean?
Eddie. I don't ca... you know.
if you're just gonna be a
little fucking pussy about it.
just take the fucking
recliner. okay?
And the Keurig. and
just fucking take the TV
that my Aunt Carol bought
us as a wedding gift.
Please. be...
Good morning. Tom Brandis.
Lizzie.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. I'm... I'll...
I'm gonna be right in.
We're not going.
like. item by item.
God. are you in my fucking
house right now. like...
like rootin' around
like a fucking raccoon.
scribbling your
name on all my shit?
Yeah. is that what you're
doing. you little raccoon fuck?
God. Eddie. I will fucking
murder you in your sleep.
Knock. knock.
Oh. good morning. Tom Brandis.
-Aleah Clinton.
-Yeah. nice to meet you. Aleah.
I got you... got you right here.
Are you from the area. Aleah?
-I grew up in Chester.
-Mm.
My family moved to the
States when I was 12.
Yikes.
I heard you FBI boys were cheap.
but this haunted
house takes the cake.
-Tom Brandis.
-Anthony Grasso.
Appreciate you
having me. Brandis.
-Sit anywhere. or assigned seating?
-I have you...
-I have you right here.
-Yeah? Alright.
Hey.
I'm Anthony.
-Aleah.
-Aleah?
"A." and then the name Leah?
Right?
-That phone call outside our fourth. Brandis?
-Yeah.
PSP Lizzie Stover.
Fuck off with my recliner.
That's... that's really all you
can do for me right now. Eddie.
Alright.
Well. on behalf of the FBI.
I wanna thank each
and every one of you
for being part of
this. uh. task force.
Um. it was a. uh.
very arduous process.
um. for selecting you.
-And. um...
-What smells?
-...the bureau feels that now...
-I'm sorry?
-...is a critical moment in this case.
-Can you smell it?
I'm sorry. I don't... I
don't know what's happening.
Uh. it's like...
smells like mildew.
It's. like. dank and...
and really skunky.
-and I just feel like...
-We all got noses. I think we're just polite enough
-not to... not to mention it.
-Hey. no. my cousin nearly got really sick
from having black
mold in her shower...
Okay. Okay. yes. Yes.
Yes. the house
definitely has a scent.
I. uh. I got some deodorizer.
so hopefully that'll lessen
the. uh. skunky. um...
Great.
Uh. there's several
rooms upstairs.
It was my thinking
that we'd each take one
and make it our office.
Uh. each of you should
have a laptop there.
The PIV card is inside of it.
Did we all have a chance to
review the brief I sent over?
-I reviewed it.
-Yeah. I read it. boss.
What brief?
The case brief detailing
what the Bureau
-expects from this operation?
-Oh. I didn't get a brief.
What... what email
did you send it to?
The one you gave
me on the phone.
Uh...
-Snickerdoodle223@yahoo.com?
-Yeah. uh...
That's the right one?
Uh... yeah. I don't know.
Maybe... maybe it went to spam.
I mean. it... it must have gone
to spam. 'cause I don't have it.
Alright. right. So.
let's take 20 minutes
and let Lizzie
familiarize herself
with the... with the
brief. and then we'll...
we'll reconvene and
talk next steps.
-Great.
-Sounds like a plan. boss.
Hey. Lizzie.
-Here's the brief.
-Yeah. Thanks.
I changed my mind. I'm
keeping that fuckin' recliner.
So far. it's been
a pitcher's duel.
Only hit coming on
an infield single.
Daly at second. Cower
looks good so far.
And the ball is still
lasting to the mid-90s.
but I'm not sure how many
more Barry will let him face.
Flores hitting .223. but
he's five for his last seven.
No.
What are you doing here?
Ahh.
Tommy?
Tommy. are you here?
You just scared away
a summer tanager.
A summer what?
What... what time
did you get in?
7 a.m. train out of Andover.
Funeral mass was at 11:00.
-How'd it go?
-Nice.
Francis gave the eulogy.
And everyone was asking for you.
Y-You're staying? You want me
to make up the bed for you?
No. no. no. no. no. I wish.
But I've got four
baptisms tomorrow.
-Come on.
-Yeah.
Let's eat. You look too skinny.
-And I got pork sandwiches.
-I look skinny?
-Yeah.
-Hot peppers?
And horseradish.
Gobs of it.
Oh. shit.
Oh. remember when
the football team...
...won the conference title
and then they
stormed the basilica.
and they picked Peter up on
his shoulders. and they...
Oh. goodness. Poor Peter!
He was coming down the
aisle with the gifts.
Oh. speaking of Peter...
-Mm.
-...he just published a piece
in the National
Catholic Register
on Rohr and the
Universal Christ.
-Mm.
-I emailed it to you.
Let me guess.
Rohr's up to his old tricks.
trying to convince us all
that Christ is in everything.
He's even in this table here.
Hello? Christ?
Hello?
Oh.
He must be taking a crap.
So. you didn't read it?
No. no more Rohr. or Rahner.
or Merton. or Augustine.
I'm... I ain't... I ain't
buying any of this shit
they're selling. anyway.
What are you reading these days?
This cup.
This Phillies cup.
It's chock full
of the most wonderful
factoids and trivia.
For example. what
Phillies player
holds the single season
title for home runs. Danny?
I grew up in Africa.
-Allen Iverson.
-Come on. Danny.
Iverson plays basketball.
Iverson could do anything.
Ryan Howard.
You should get one
of these yourself.
It's like a 57-year-old
man's prostate.
Come on.
So. what's new at work?
Kathleen wants me.
Special Agent Tom Brandis.
to head up a task force.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
Yeah.
Love this song. Remember
this from Merrimack?
Of course. I remember it.
What kind of task force?
Our mission. which we've
been strong-armed to accept.
is to take down a
group of thieves
that have been terrorizing area
drug houses. don't you know?
-Thieves?
-In Halloween masks.
Very scary shit.
Blood and guts are being
spilled on the streets
of Delaware County. Danny
boy. and goddamn it...
me and my crack team are
gonna put an end to it.
♪ Big storm is coming ♪
♪ There's thunder
and lightning ♪
♪ Better hold on ♪
♪ Watch out! ♪
♪ Task force is coming ♪
♪ Thunder and lightning ♪
♪ You better hold on ♪
Come on. Danny. take
that collar off.
Come on. dance. Now...
now. you're just a man.
Come on. Danny. Don't
leave me hangin'. baby.
Yeah. Danny.
What happened?
Oh. boy. I think I'm leaning.
Huh?
Come on.
Oh. my God.
Let me fix your...
There you go.
Get some rest.
I've seen him like this before.
Yeah. wasted? Me too.
He'll find his way.
Fuck!
Where's the money?
So. you're the ones that's been
causing all the problems. huh?
Get your fucking hands off me!
Get the fuck off me. you fuck!
-Go! Go!
-Fuck off!
Ow! You fucking fuckers!
Assholes!
I've got it fucking coming
for you. you little fucker!
I'm gonna rip your fucking
hearts out of your chest!
You motherfucker!
Leave me alone!
Get the fuck off me!
I saw his face. That one there.
I saw that one's
ugly fucking face.
I lost my gun.
Uh-oh. boys.
Even I can tell things
haven't gone as planned.
Now we've seen his
ugly fuckin' face.
And trust me. we don't forget
a face that fuckin' ugly.
Where's the money?
Wait. I know that voice.
I fucking know you. man.
Joanne. whose fucking
voice is that?
Where's the fucking money?!
I fucking know you. man.
I fucking know you. man!
-Stay here.
-I fucking know you!
Come on. come on. come on.
Hurry the fuck up!
What's going on?
Fuck.
Oh. now you're really fucked.
Hurry up. guys!
There's somebody here.
Let's go. We gotta go.
-Give me your gun.
-What are you talking about?
Give me your fucking gun!
I got it. You find the money.
Hey. D. you ready?
Warren! Warren!
We should head out if we want
to make it in time. brother.
D?
What's going on? D!
Warren!
D! Talk to me.
Hey. hey. Scissors. Scissors!
Behind you!
♪ Win big. mama's fallen angel ♪
♪ Lose big. living
out her lies ♪
♪ Wants it all.
mama's fallen angel ♪
♪ Lose it all. rolling
the dice of her life ♪
♪ Win big. mama's fallen angel ♪
♪ Lose big. living
out her lies ♪
♪ Wants it all.
mama's fallen angel ♪
♪ Lose it all. rolling
the dice of her life ♪
♪ Win big. mama's fallen angel ♪
♪ Lose big. living
out her lies ♪
♪ Wants it all.
mama's fallen angel ♪
♪ Lose it all. rolling
the dice of her life ♪
♪ Win big ♪
Come on. let's go. We
get the fuck out of here.
What are you doing. man?
Are you my dad's friends?
Uh...
Yeah. Yeah. we're his friends.
Did you hear fireworks?
Yeah. we heard them. too.
Hello?
Hey. boss. it's Grasso.
Uh. we got four bodies out
here at 18 Chapel Road.
Um. it looks like
the same crew.
Fuck.
-Yeah?
-Uh. hey. it's Grasso again.
-Yeah.
-Um. I'm at the scene now. We're just getting word
there might have been a kid
inside the house last night.
Patrol's canvassing
the neighborhood now.
but doesn't sound like
anyone saw anything.
Is Lizzie here?
PSP Snickerdoodle has yet to
grace us with her presence.
Damnit.
What's he doing in
the basement. anyway?
His father made him sleep
there when he acted up.
I was just talking to
one of the neighbors.
And we're sure the boy
was here last night?
Yeah. same neighbor said
his son rode bikes with Sam
around 6 p.m.
He was here.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm